const STORE = [
  {
    question: 'From which country did ballet originate?',
    answers: [
      'Russia',
      'France',
      'England',
      'Italy'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Italy'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who introduced ballet to France?',
    answers: [
      'Pyotr Ilyich Tchaikovsky',
      'Leonardo DaVinci',
      'Catherine de Medici',
      'George Balanchine'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Catherine de Medici'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which French king danced in ballet performances?',
    answers: [
      'Francis I',
      'Henry IV',
      'Louis XIV',
      'Louis XVI'
      ],
    correctAnswer: 'Louis XIV'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is a ballerina?',
    answers: [
      'A female who dances for a professional ballet company',
      'A female dancer of the highest rank in a ballet company',
      'A female dancer who has trained in ballet for at least 5 years',
      'A female dancer who performs ballet on stage'
      ],
    correctAnswer: 'A female dancer of the highest rank in a ballet company',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is a male ballet dancer called?',
    answers: [
      'Ballerino',
      'Danseur',
      'Balletomane',
      'Allegro'
      ],
    correctAnswer: 'Danseur'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is is the technical term for dancing on the tips of the toes?',
    answers: [
      'on point',
      'pointilism',
      'pointing the toes',
      'en pointe', 
      ],
    correctAnswer: 'en pointe'
  },
  {
    question: 'What are pointe shoes typically made out of?',
    answers: [
      'layers of fabric | glue | satin | hard leather',
      'layers of fabric | clay | satin | particle board',
      'layers of fabric | glue | silk | wood',
      'layers of fabric | cement | silk | plastic'
      ],
    correctAnswer: 'layers of fabric | glue | satin | hard leather'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the minimum age a student must be before they start training en pointe?',
    answers: [
      '7 years old',
      '10 years old',
      '12 years old',
      '15 years old'
      ],
    correctAnswer: '12 years old'
  },
  {
    question: 'How long does it typically take to become a professional ballet dancer?',
    answers: [
      '1-2 years',
      '3-5 years',
      '6-7 years',
      '8-10 years'
      ],
    correctAnswer: '8-10 years'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following is NOT a ballet movement?',
    answers: [
      'sashé', 
      'lame duck', 
      'port de bras', 
      'balonné' 
      ],
    correctAnswer: 'sashé'
  }
];